<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Ne Travaillez Jamais</string>

    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="stop">Stop</string>

    <string name="permission_not_granted">Permission to block screen not granted. Exiting.</string>

    <string name="text_title">Don\'t work, ever</string>
    <string name="text_explanation_1">
        This app allows you to limit the time and frequency of use of your mobile device, blocking it completely.
    </string>
    <string name="text_explanation_2">
        Set the following parameters and protect your time and your mind. Don\'t become a subject of performance.
    </string>

    <string name="details">Details</string>
    <string name="detail_text_1" formatted="false">The app uses a time bucket to know when to block the device. The bucket has the size of your "max continuous time" (%s).</string>
    <string name="detail_text_2" formatted="false">When you use your device, the bucket drains, and when it is not used, it fills. The drain and fill rates are determined by your target time (%s).</string>
    <string name="detail_text_3" formatted="false">With the current settings, the fill rate is about %d times slower than the drain rate, so for every %d minutes that the device is off, you will get 1 minute of use time.</string>
    <string name="detail_text_4" formatted="false">When the bucket is empty, the device is blocked until the bucket is filled back to half its capacity. With the current settings, that would be %d minutes.</string>
    <string name="detail_text_5"                  >Also, to discourage compulsive use, just unlocking the device counts as 1 minute of use.</string>

    <string name="param_total_screen_on">Target time per day</string>
    <string name="max_screen_on_time">Max continuous time</string>
    <string name="minutes">minutes</string>
    <string name="hour">hour</string>
    <string name="hours">hours</string>

    <string name="quote">
        \"Digital devices bring a new type of coercion, a new form of slavery.
        They exploit us more efficiently since, by virtue of their mobility, transform any place in a workplace, and any time in work time.
        The freedom of mobility is exchanged for the fatal coercion of having to work everywhere.\"
    </string>

    <string name="author" translatable="false">&#8212; Byung Chul Han</string>
    <string name="show_quote">Show quote</string>
    <string name="about">About this app</string>

    <string name="about_text"><b>Ne Travaillez Jamais</b> has been developed by\n<a href="http://pauek.info">Pau Fernández</a> (<a href="https://twitter.com/pauek">@pauek</a>)
        in collaboration with <a href="http://www.pacochanivet.com">Paco Chanivet</a>
        for his project\n\"<a href="http://www.adngaleria.com/web/pag/pfitxa_img.asp?t=2&amp;id=3068&amp;o=4&amp;la=en">8 Acts Working Day</a>\".
    </string>
    <string name="source">
        The source code can be found at:\n<a href="https://github.com/pauek/DontWork">github.com/pauek/DontWork</a>.
    </string>

</resources>
